http://www.capacitas.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Capacitas is committed to ensuring the privacy of users and customers of our website and services; this policy describes our commitment to privacy.
This privacy policy applies only to the capacitas.co.uk website. We at Capacitas respect your right to privacy and so invite you to browse the website without revealing who you are or registering with us.
Home
Privacy Policy
The privacy policy sets out how Capacitas uses and protects and information that you give to us when using this website.
If you have any questions about your privacy when using our website, please dpo@capacitas.co.uk or call 0207 566 4869
What personal information we collect
We collect any personal information you voluntarily give us and that personally identifies you including contact information such as your name, email address, company name, address, phone number and other information about yourself or your business.
Methods of collection
We collect personal information from you when you submit online forms on our website, email us with an enquiry, or call us.
We also collect information automatically about your visit to our website, which may become paired with your personal information, please see our cookies section for more information.
How we use your personal information
We may process your personal information to:
Improve your experience when using our website by personalising the content you see
Send you information by email, post or other means, relating to our business
Maintain internal records
Our lawful basis for processing your information in this way is our legitimate interest in marketing our services to you.
We will never sell your personal information to any third party and will not share your data with any other data controllers unless compelled to do so by law.
Email marketing
Our use of your personal data may include occasional email marketing.
You may opt out of any of our email marketing types using the email preferences centre accessible from links at the bottom of any marketing email we send, or by dpo@capacitas.co.uk or calling 0207 566 4869.
External websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Access to your personal information
You have the right to access any information we hold about you.
To request access please email dpo@capacitas.co.uk using the email address we hold for you or otherwise proving your identity.
We will provide the information free of charge and within one month, except in the event that the request is unfounded, excessive or repetitive, in which case we reserve the right to charge a proportionate administration fee or refuse.
Rectification of personal information
If any of the information we hold on you is inaccurate or incomplete, you make ask us to correct or complete it at any time.
Your right of erasure, or to be forgotten
You may request the deletion of any email we hold on you at any time.
Be aware that requesting deletion, unlike unsubscribing from specific emails, is total and irreversible. This means that we will also lose record of you having ever been on our systems, including any previous instructions you have given us opting out of specific emails types. If you re-join our systems, by voluntarily providing your personal information, you will appear to us as a completely new data subject. This does not affect your other rights in any way.
To request deletion of your personal information, dpo@capacitas.co.uk using the email address we hold for you or otherwise proving your identity.
We will delete your information for free and within one moth of receiving your request, except in the event that the request is unfounded, excessive or repetitive, in which case we reserve the right to charge a proportionate administration fee or refuse.
Cookies
Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites.
We use a combination of  session cookies and persistent cookies in order to track how you use and experience our website, build anonymous statistical data about how our website is performing, and to power the personalisation of website content to you.
The types of cookie you can expect to see in use on our website are from:
HubSpot - our marketing automation and CRM system
Cloudflare - web performance and security software deployed by HubSpot
Google Analytics - statistical analysis of website performance
Facebook - advertising and targeting provider
Hotjar - anonymous visitor recordings and interaction heatmaps
You can choose to accept or decline cookies in your browser settings. Declining the use of cookies may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Capacitas Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 11/05/2018.
Job Applicant additional Privacy Notice
As part of any recruitment process, Capacitas Ltd collects and processes personal data relating to job applicants. The organisation is committed to being transparent about how it collects and uses that data and to meeting its data protection obligations. For details on the full policy and how we manage your data click here.
Navigation
Prepare for Peak
Control Cloud Costs
Continuous Performance
Find Us
Capacitas Ltd
69 Turnmill Street,
London, EC1M 5RR,
